coka@fastmail.com | https://github.com/coka

Summary

My primary area of expertise is computer graphics, and creative coding is my primary passion. I have a solid understanding of the graphics pipeline (transformations, illumination models, and GPU acceleration). Somewhere along the way, this turned into crafting UIs using functional programming and SVGs, but hey, at least it's visual. I would love to work with <code>ClojureScript</code>, <code>ReasonML</code>, or <code>Elm</code> on real projects. I want to connect the pieces between software engineering and computer graphics in order to create meaningful programs.

Experience

Simple Task (Oct 2019-)

Working on mobile applications. **Skills:** React, React Native, Redux, RxJS, TypeScript, Vue.js.

LambdaWorks (Nov 2018-Jul 2019)

Frontend stuff. Mostly React. Built products with people. Worked as the only frontend developer on a product team, from ideation to MVP launch, informing various design decisions along the way. **Skills:** React, Redux, RXJS, TypeScript.

DevTech (Apr 2016-Nov 2018)

Worked on integrating IaaS systems. Later, worked remotely for a London-based fintech startup on their product. Helped shape DevTech's R&D and internal education efforts. Skills: C#, F#, Microsoft SQL Server, Entity Framework, SignalR, TypeScript, React, Redux.

Rendered Text (Jul 2015-Oct 2015)

Internship

Worked on the user-facing part of SemaphoreCI. Learned a lot about OOP, BDD, and software design. I had the privilege of working alongside colleagues with various backgrounds, which motivated me to figure out how to communicate technical ideas effectively. Skills: Ruby on Rails, CoffeeScript, AngularJS (1.x), Vagrant.

3Lateral (Aug 2012-Sep 2012)

Internship

Struggled with making an animation-ready character face from scanned data, and had the wonderful opportunity to experience a production environment first-hand. Skills: Maya, MEL, Python, ZBrush.

Education

Faculty of Technical Sciences, University of Novi Sad (2011-2019)

Bachelor of Computer Graphics 8.22/10.00 (never graduated)

Cambridge Certificate of Proficiency in English (2010)

79/100 (Grade B)

Jovan Jovanović Zmaj Grammar School, Novi Sad (2007-2011)

Natural Sciences

4.64/5.00, with honors (physics, music)

Other

Resonate (Apr 2014-Apr 2017)

Over the years, I have attended several workshops at the Resonate festival in Belgrade. In 2015, I earned a scholarship for an advanced workshop of choice. These workshops were themed around interactive real-time graphics. We used various creating coding frameworks and programming languages to achieve an aesthetic result, often on constrained platforms, such as the Raspberry Pi. Skills: three.js, Polymer, WebGL, OpenGL 4.x, OpenGL ES, openFrameworks.